Now you know it hurts.
الآن أنت تعلم أنه مؤلم.
Second brother is also anxious,
الأخ الثاني قلق أيضًا ،
husband,
الزوج،
Don't blame him, okay?
لا تلومه ، حسنًا؟
Dear,
عزيزي،
you are such a good person.
أنت شخص جيد.
-Send me a good person
- أرسل لي شخصًا جيدًا
card. -No,
بطاقة.  -رقم،
You know I'm not.
أنت تعرف أنني لست كذلك.
Me,
أنا،
I didn't mean that.
لم أقصثد ذلك
Your Ladyship,
سيدتك ،
I understand.
أفهم.
I really didn't mean that.
أنا حقا لم أقصد ذلك.
You … You don't know how to be ashamed.
أنت ... لا تعرف كيف تخجل.
Kiss
قبلة
and hug.
و عناق.
Now you're turning against him.
الآن أنت تنقلب عليه.
Stay here.
ابق هنا.
Don't run around.
لا تركض.
Go back to your work.
عد إلى عملك.
Don't worry about me.
لا تقلق علي.
Why is your face so red?
لماذا وجهك أحمر جدا؟
Why is your heart beating so fast?
لماذا ينبض قلبك بهذه السرعة؟
Just go.
فقط اذهب.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
Who wants to wait for you?
من يريد أن ينتظرك؟
Su Qiu, you're back.
سو تشيو ، لقد عدت.
My Lady,
سيدتي،
I heard about your marriage.
سمعت عن زواجك.
Second Young Master worked day and night,
عمل السيد الشاب الثاني ليل نهار ،
and rushed for several days before he came back from Muyun City.
وهرع لعدة أيام قبل أن يعود من مدينة مويون.
He didn't even rest.
لم يرتاح حتى.
With such a mess,
مع هذه الفوضى ،
he might get punished when he returns.
قد يعاقب عند عودته.
Why don't you go home for me?
لماذا لا تذهب للمنزل من أجلي؟
Please intercede with father and brother for me.
تشفع لي مع الأب والأخ.
Yes, Miss.
نعم آنستي.
Leave it to me.
اتركه لي.
My lady,
سيدتي،
Miss, look!
افتقد النظر!
See you in Fanlou tomorrow.
نراكم غدا في فانلو.
Zhi, please listen to the book.
زهي ، من فضلك استمع إلى الكتاب.
Lord Zhang told you to go out tomorrow and listen to Ben,
قال لك اللورد تشانغ أن تخرج غدًا وتستمع إلى بن ،
That's not good, right?
هذا ليس جيدًا ، أليس كذلك؟
My husband will be unhappy if he finds out.
سيكون زوجي غير سعيد إذا اكتشف ذلك.
You,
أنت،
Why do you care?
لماذا تهتم؟
This is the latest script.
هذا هو أحدث سيناريو.
The premiere is tomorrow.
العرض الأول غدا.
It's hard to get a ticket?
من الصعب الحصول على تذكرة؟
The scalper ticket has sold for 100 taels of gold.
بيعت تذكرة المستغل مقابل 100 تايل من الذهب.
Look,
نظرة،
is that the story of Ye Jiajun?
هل هذه قصة يي جياجون؟
Come and have a look.
يأتي وننظر لها.
Second Young Master specially brought back
استعاد السيد الشاب الثاني خصيصًا
special products from Muyun City?
منتجات خاصة من مدينة مويون؟
I also heard that
سمعت ذلك أيضًا
Fanlou is offering a special package for the premiere tomorrow,
تقدم Fanlou حزمة خاصة للعرض الأول غدًا ،
Roasted chicken set meal
وجبة مجموعة دجاج مشوي
is only available at the premiere.
متاح فقط في العرض الأول.
Only for the premiere,
فقط من أجل العرض الأول ،
I'll ask my husband.
سأطلب من زوجي.
No way.
مستحيل.
If you ask,
إذا سألت،
His Lordship won't let us go.
سيادته لن تسمح لنا بالرحيل.
Miss,
يغيب،
go ahead.
إنطلق.
Okay,
تمام،
I knew you were the best.
كنت أعلم أنك الأفضل.
Dear guests, please go back.
الضيوف الأعزاء ، يرجى العودة.
I can't sit in there anymore.
لا أستطيع الجلوس هناك بعد الآن.
Come back tomorrow.
عد غدا.
Look at you. It's all
انظر لحالك.  كل شئ
because you're late to come back tomorrow.
لأنك تأخرت في العودة غدًا.
They're all sold out.
تم بيعها كلها.
What do you think we should do? Come back tomorrow.
ماذا تعتقد أنه يجب علينا فعله؟  عد غدا.
Speaking of Ye Jiajun,
بالحديث عن يي جياجون ،
pick any one of them.
اختر أي واحد منهم.
That's the top one. This guy
هذا هو الأول.  هذا الشخص
Ye Xiao Lang,
يي شياو لانغ ،
At the age of 15,
في سن ال 15 ،
he broke into the enemy camp alone.
اقتحم معسكر العدو وحده.
He cut off the cloud flag of Xiliang Dog Thief with one sword
قطع علم سحابة Xiliang Dog Thief بسيف واحد
Okay.
تمام.
Well said,
احسنت القول،
Zhi,
زي ،
do you know how the Ye Army treats you and me?
هل تعرف كيف يعاملك جيش يي وأنا؟
And... it's a distant story,
و ... إنها قصة بعيدة ،
and... it's ours,
و ... إنها لنا ،
With your current relationship with Wei Shangzhi,
مع علاقتك الحالية مع Wei Shangzhi ،
if you know the truth,
إذا كنت تعرف الحقيقة ،
What should I do? Yes,
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟  نعم،